

340, Mokdongseo-ro, Yangcheon-gu, Seoul, 08089, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-9686-8177 | ■ tyoung96@naver.com | ★ taeyoung96.github.io | □ Taeyoung96

"Nothing ventured, nothing gained."

Summary.

This is Taeyoung Kim, who wants to become an autonomous driving or robotics SW engineer. My research interests are Computer Vision and Sensor Fusion. I like to take on challenging tasks and I like to grow up with my colleagues around me. That's why I record and share what I did on my Github or Technical Blog. I would like to participate in changing the world with advanced science and technology.

Research Interests

Computer Vision Object Detection, Segmentation, Depth Estimation

Sensor Fusion Combination of camera, lidar, and radar

Education

Kwang Woon University

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022 (Expected)

- Current GPA: 4.07 / 4.50, Current Major GPA: 4.50 / 4.50
- Club: BARAM (Robotics Academic Group) [2020 Staff], DAISY (English Conversation Club) [2019 Spring President]

Work Experience _

KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT INTERN (ADVISOR: DR. KANGGUN KIM)

• Research on Monocular Depth Estimation

Sep. 2020 - Present

• Participated in KIST disinfect robot (AI Disinfection Robot) project

Image Process System Lab @Kwang Woon Univ

Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2020

Undergraduate Lab Intern (Advisor: Prof. Donggyu Sim)

- · Research on Image Processing based on Deep learning
- Participated in seminars related to Deep Learning and Image Processing

Honors & Awards ___

AWARDS

2020.11	Dean's List, KwangWoon University	Seoul, S.Korea
2020.9	5th Place on B-track , Korea Health Datathon 2020	Seoul, S.Korea
2019.10	Dean's List, KwangWoon University	Seoul, S.Korea

HONORS

2020-2	National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship (Full tuition Scholarship),	Seoul, S.Korea
2020-2	Korea Student Aid Foundation	Seoul, S.Noreu
2020-1	${\bf National\ Science\ and\ Engineering\ Undergraudate\ Scholarship\ (Full\ tuition\ Scholarship)},$	Seoul. S.Korea

Korea Student Aid Foundation

2019-2 Full tuition Scholarship, KwangWoon University Seoul, S.Korea

Skills

Programming C++/C, Python, JAVA, Matlab **Framework** Pytorch, Tensorflow, Keras

DevOps Git, Docker, ROS Languages Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity

WRITERS

Technical Blogs Github blog

• Writing some posts about lecture summary, paper review, some tips for developments.

To share what I have studied with others and to remember it longer.

Monocular Depth Estimation with ORB-SLAM2

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

Personal Toy Project

I was curious about the performance of the recent depth estimation model.

- I used 'Monocular Depth Estimation with Transfer Learning pretrained MobileNetV2' model and applied to ORB-SLAM2 also compared with ORB-SLAM2(Monocular mode), ORB-SLAM2(RGB-D mode)
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository].

KCCV 2020 Korea computer vision society

Participant Aug. 2020

• Participated to know about the trend of Computer Vision

Using deep learning for data analysis and image processing (Basic)

Korea open source software

Jul. 2020

May. 2020 - Present

Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020

• Studied lectures which is related to the using Deep learning framework(Keras)

Runner Alarm System based on Deep Learning

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

Personal Toy Project Apr. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- I wanted to distinguish between walking children and running children with an object detection model.
- When children are running for an amount of time, a beep sounds.
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository].